嘿  俗话说得没错
Hey. Hey. Wow, it is true what they say:
怀孕的腹部像个大鼓
Pregnant bellies look like a drum.
我的肚子大得连吉他也拿不了了
Well, it's just I'm so pregnant that my guitar doesn't fit anymore.
所以我想  生产前我打算用鼓来伴奏了
So I thought, till I'm not, I'm gonna play my songs on this drum.
听来很不错
It sounds really cool.
听  听  你们听
Listen, listen. Ahem. Okay.
臭臭猫  臭臭猫
Smelly cat, smelly cat
他们喂你吃什么
What are they feeding you?
菲比  听起来不错啊
Wow, Pheebs, that sounds great.
我知道  而且我才练了1小时
I know, I know! And I've only been playing for, like, an hour.
菲比  菲比  嗨
Phoebe. Phoebe. Hi. Hey.
你怎么来了
What are you doing here?
我来请你给我帮个大忙
Um, actually I came down to ask you a big favor.
别说你还想塞东西进来啊
Oh, well, don't tell me you want to keep more of your stuff in my uterus.
不  不  不  是这样的
No, no, no. Okay. Now, see. Ahem.
我想给女孩取名莱丝莉
I want to name the girl baby Leslie.
法兰克想叫其中一个男孩
And, um, Frank wants to name one of the boy babies...
法兰克二世二世
...Frank Jr., Jr.
那不就是法兰克三世
Wouldn't that be Frank III?
说了我就有气
Don't get me started.
无论如何  既然有三个孩子
Anyway, um, since there are three babies...
我们起了其中的两个
...and, um, we both got to put our names in...
我们非常荣幸  想请你替另一个男孩命名
...we would be truly honored if you would name the other boy baby.
哇啊 哦
Oh, wow.
好棒  太好了
That's so nice. Oh, oh! Ha, ha.
美洲狮
Cougar.
你再想一下
You think about it.
老友记  第四季  第18集  瑞秋的新装
Friends S04E18  The One With Rachel's New Dress
主演: 珍妮佛·安妮斯顿
主演: 寇妮·考克斯
主演: 丽莎·库卓
主演: 麦特·勒布兰
主演: 马修·派瑞
主演: 大卫·修蒙
我有一件胸罩还在晾着呢
I left a bra drying on the shower rod.
你儿子会不会以为那是你的  而心灵受创
You don't think your son will think it's yours and be traumatized?
妈咪可以有老婆  爸比就可以有胸罩
Hey, Mommy can have a wife. Daddy can have a bra.
该走了
Oh, it's time to go.
不  不  不  那钟有点快的
Oh, no, no, no. See, that clock's a little fast.
我们还有17分钟
Uh, we still have 17 minutes.
什么事可以在17分钟内
Huh. What can we do in 17 minutes...
做两次
...twice?
哎  你的野心真大
Well, that's ambitious.
别理它  是卡萝带你儿子来了
Okay, you can ignore that. That's Carol with your son.
相信我  他长大点的话就会明白了
Uh, believe me, when he's older, he'll understand.
罗斯   马上来
Ross. I'll be right there.
你好  嗨
Hello. Hello. Hey. Hi.
艾蜜莉   这是卡萝和苏珊
Uh, Emily, this is Carol and Susan.
总算见到你  我也是
Hey, it's so nice to finally meet you. You too.
苏珊下星期要去伦敦拍广告
Susan's gonna be shooting a commercial in London next week.
我好兴奋  还没去过
I'm so excited. I've never been there.
我可以带你到处去  太好了
Oh, well, I'll show you around. Great.
我还想看秀  你有什么建议
Also, I was hoping to catch a show. So if you can make any suggestions...
有很多都很棒的
Oh, there's tons of terrific stuff.
我陪你去
I'll go with you. Oh.
对不起
Oh, I'm sorry.
你们可真聊得来
Oh. Look at you two bonding.
去机场都快来不及了  你没事吧
Making us late for the airport so... Are you all right?
他没事  没事  他不喜欢我们相处得好
Oh, he's fine, he's fine. It's just us getting along is difficult for him...
因为他不喜欢我
...because he doesn't like me.
拜托   没错
Ha, ha. Come on. That's...
是真的
It's true.
嗨   名字想好了吗
Hi. Hey. Hey, do we have a baby name yet?
还没有  好难喔
Ugh, no. It's so hard.
翻遍了这本书也找不到
I went through this whole book and found nothing.
我想取个勇猛而有自信的名字
I want a name that's really, like, you know, strong and confident.
例如爱克爽
You know? Like Exxon.
很适合瓦尔迪兹的小孩
Well, it certainly worked for that Valdez kid.
菲比  你要勇猛的名字  绿巨人怎么样
Oh, oh, Pheebs. You want a strong name? How about The Hulk?
不  不喜欢绿巨人
No, I'm not sure about Hulk...
不过我喜欢什么"人"的
...but I like the idea of a name starting with "The."
想取好名字  就取乔伊
Well, you want a good name, heh, go with Joey.
乔伊是好朋友  好兄弟
Joey's your pal, Joey's your buddy.
人都在哪里  都跟乔伊一起出去了
Where is everybody? They're hanging out with Joey.
知道什么啊  要取乔伊
Know what? If you're gonna name him Joey...
还不如取钱德
...you should name him Chandler.
少来啊  钱德风趣  世故  一旦了解他
Oh, come on, Chandler's funny, he's sophisticated, and he's very lovable...
就会觉得他很可爱
...once you get to know him.
乔伊也很可爱
Hey, Joey's lovable too.
重要的是当你需要乔伊  他就会出现
But the thing about Joey is, if you need him, he'll be there.
钱德也会出现  只是会慢一点
Chandler will be there for you too. I mean, he might be a little late...
不过他一定会出现  而且还会带冰汽水过来
...but he'll be there. And he'll bring you some cold soda...
如果你在很热的时候需要他的话
...if what you need him for is that you're really hot.
你觉得呢  你觉得呢
What do you say? What do you say?
跟心爱的人同名的想法很好
Well, I like the idea of naming him after someone I love.
而且乔伊和钱德都是很棒的名字
And Joey and Chandler are both great names.
但是我不想
All right, I don't...
或者就叫绿巨人好了
Maybe I will just name him The Hulk.
我真不该提起我想给我的孩子起名
I knew I shouldn't have mentioned it. That's what I wanted to name my kid.
嗨  莫妮卡  如果你今晚想和约书亚睡
Hey, Mon? If you were hoping to sleep with Joshua for the first time tonight...
你会挑哪件
...which one of these would you want to be wearing?
我觉得帮别人挑性感睡衣很怪
You know what? It really creeps me out choosing other people's sex clothes.
对不起  我太兴奋了
Sorry. I'm just so excited.
我等了好几个月了  我还跑去染发
I've been waiting for this for months. I got my hair colored.
我买了新鞋子  还帮他煮大餐
I got new sheets. I'm making him a very fancy meal.
看我给他准备了什么
What am I making him, by the way?
什锦沙拉  有羊酪  松子
Well, you're making him a fris¨¦e salad with goat cheese and pine nuts...
菰米饭  烤庐笋和鲑鱼面包丁
...wild rice, roasted asparagus and salmon en croute.
我不是要做腓力牛排吗
I thought I was making him filet mignon.
本来是  但餐厅的鲑鱼有剩   所以你决定煮鲑鱼
Yeah, you were, but you decided to make salmon because you had some left over.
然后你想到要是你抱怨   "你"就不会煮了
And then you realized if you bitched about it, then you would stop cooking...
你就得上烤马铃薯加健怡可乐
...and you would have to make your famous baked potato and Diet Coke.
"我" 煮菜时火气可真大
Wow, I really get crabby when I cook.
嘿   嘿
Hey. Hey.
嘿
Hey.
艾蜜莉昨晚打电话来
So, uh, Emily called last night.
你现在才转告我
And now you're giving me the message?
结果艾蜜莉爱死苏珊了
Turns out that Emily is just crazy about Susan.
她们一起去看戏
Yeah. They're going to the theater together.
她们一起吃晚饭
They're going to dinner.
她们一起去骑马
They're going horseback riding.
苏珊真会玩
God, Susan is so fun.
好像这个太相似了一点
Look, this is just a little too familiar.
我和卡萝分手前整整半年
Okay, for, like, six months before Carol and I split up...
我整天只听到 "我朋友苏珊好聪明
...all I heard was, "My friend Susan is so smart.
我朋友苏珊好风趣  我朋友苏珊好棒"
My friend Susan is so funny. My friend Susan is so great."
你觉得艾蜜莉和苏珊之间会擦出火花
You actually think that something could happen between Emily and Susan?
她们都一起上健身房了
Hey, they're going to the gym together.
两个女人
Two women...
劈腿
...stretching.
她们洗蒸汽浴  开始互相逗弄
You know, they take a steam together, things get a little playful.
你们没看过《登峰造极》吗
Didn't you see Personal Best?
没  但我一定要看
No, but I'm gonna.
先生  你疯了
Hi. Hi. You're crazy.
她是艾蜜莉   艾蜜莉是异性恋
Okay, this is Emily. Emily is straight.
你怎么知道
How do you know?
我们结婚前原以为卡萝是异性恋
I mean, we thought Carol was straight before I married her.
我肯定  不喜欢罗斯这个名字
Yeah, definitely. I don't like the name Ross.
你落井下石的方式还真怪
What a weird way to kick me when I'm down.
我是说宝宝的名字
No, no, I just meant for the baby.
罗斯有什么不好
What's wrong with Ross?
就像绿巨人
It's just, you know, something like this...
就不会遇上这种事吗
...would never happen to The Hulk, you know.
谁说的  那不真实
Actually, that's not true.
《绿巨人》第72集里  布鲁斯班纳博士发现
In The Incredible Hulk, number 72, Dr. Bruce Banner found...
难以置信  我女朋友是同性恋
You know, never mind. My girlfriend's a lesbian.
所以我决定取名字不是乔伊就是钱德
So I decided I'm definitely gonna go with either Joey or Chandler.
啊哦  啊哦
Oh. oh, oh, oh.
你一定要选乔伊
You gotta pick Joey.
有哪个名人叫钱德
I mean, name one famous person named Chandler.
雷蒙钱德勒  你捏造的人不算
Raymond Chandler. Someone you didn't make up.
叫乔伊的才没有名人  除了
Okay, there are no famous Joeys. Except for, heh...
乔伊巴塔富寇
...Joey Buttafuoco.
他的确是我们的心头之痛
Yeah, that guy really hurt us. Yeah.
那这样  加起来除以二如何
Well, how about a compromise then? Okay, what if it's...
例如  钱道伊
...you know, Chan-no-ey?
乔伊  你想嘛  他绝对当不上总统
Okay, look, Joey? Come on, think about it. He'll never be president.
绝对不会出现乔伊总统
I mean, there's never gonna be a President Joey.
听着  我本来不想提的
All right, look, I didn't want to bring this up.
但钱德是我听过最蠢的名字
But Chandler is the stupidest name I've heard in my life.
它根本不是名字  连个词都不是
It's not even a name. It's barely even a word.
它有点接近钱包  但又不是
Okay, it's kind of like chandelier but it's not.
它是个蠢到爆的名字  笨蛋  它不是名字
All right? It's a stupid, stupid, non-name.
你说得对  我的名字烂透了
You're right. I have a horrible, horrible name.
对不起  我不是  对不起
I'm sorry, man. I didn't... I'm sorry.
所以我想就该用乔伊
So I guess it's Joey, then. I mean...
真好  谢谢你这么费心
This is so nice. Thank you for doing this.
别客气  烹饪能舒缓我的心
Oh. Please. Cooking soothes me.
吃吧  好的
So dig in. All right.
看起来都很好吃
Well, it all looks so good. Mm.
天哪
Oh, my God.
我知道  天哪  这个饭好
Oh, I know. My God, this rice is so...
我的手艺真好
I am so good.
你后面
Behind you.
没事  他们以前就住这里  有时会迁徙回来
Oh, yeah, sorry. They used to live here, and sometimes they migrate back over.
能不能让他们不要在这里
Is there, uh...? Is there some way that they could, uh, not be here?
只是  我最怕家禽了
It's just that, uh, farm birds really kind of freak me out.
啊  好的
Yeah. Okay, okay.
出去  出去
Here we go. Here we go. Whoa.
哇啊  抱歉
Whoa. Oh, sorry.
出去
There you go.
耶  你们怎么会敲门
Hey. How'd you do that?
进来
Come on.
都走了
All gone. Heh.
只是敏感家禽  是吧
So, farm birds, huh?
我只有这个怪癖   我发誓
Yeah, it's my only weird thing, I swear.
我该已经告诉过你了  但我不知道这里会有鸡鸭
And I would have told you about it but I didn't know that they'd be here.
要不要来点
So can I serve you a little...
怎么了  怎么了
What, what, what?
没事  只是我知道它们还在外面
Nothing. Uh, it's just that I know that they're still out there.
他们在对门  隔着两道墙
They're across the hall. I mean, that's two doors away.
它们要啄很久才能把墙啄穿  过来
It's gonna take them a long time to peck their way back over here.
一点也不好笑
That's not funny.
是吗  要不
Uh... Okay, you know...
要不换个地方  会让你好受点
Would you feel better if we went someplace else?
我们可以把东西打包去你家
I mean, we could pack all this stuff up and, you know, go to your apartment.
我家正在装修   一团混乱
Oh, they're working on it this week. It's a mess.
不过  我们可以去我父母家
But, uh, I'm staying at my parents' house. We could go there.
你父母家  他们出国了
Your parents'? They're out of town.
对
Oh.
那里地方很大  视野很宽阔
It's a huge place, and it's got this gorgeous view of the park.
会非常  非常地浪漫
It'd be very, very romantic.
你觉得如何  好啊
What do you say? Yeah, that works.
它们闻得出恐惧
They can smell the fear.
嗨
Hey.
班好吗
How's Ben?
我问他吃不吃东西  他说不要
Well, I asked him if he wanted to eat. He said no.
我问他要不要睡觉  他说不要
I asked him if he wanted to sleep. He said no.
我问他想做什么  他说不要
I asked what he wanted to do. He said no.
所以他在扫地
So he's sweeping.
嘿  宝贝
Hey, buddy. Hey.
有苏珊的消息吗
So, um, any word from Susan?
她说她跟艾蜜莉玩得很开心
Ooh, yeah, she said she's having so much fun with Emily.
对了  你有没有想过
Uh, by the by, did it ever occur to you that...
她们或许玩的太开心了一点
...I don't know, maybe they might be having a little too much fun?
什么叫太开心
What's too much fun?
我们结婚时  你和苏珊的那种闲心
You know, the kind of fun you and Susan had when we were married.
天哪  你还真会乱想
Oh, my God. You are so paranoid.
是  是吗
Am I? Yes.
是吗
Am I?
艾蜜莉我不知道
I can't speak for Emily...
但苏珊和我的关系很稳定
...but Susan is in a loving, committed relationship.
卡萝  我们也是
Uh-huh. Carol, so were we.
你想像一下
All right, just imagine for a moment...
苏珊认识了别人  然后一拍即合
...that Susan meets someone, and they really hit it off.
她们从剧院回来
Say they're coming back from the theater...
然后去酒吧喝个小酒
...and they stop at a pub for a couple of drinks.
有说有笑
They're laughing, you know.
有人有意无意地碰了另外一个人
Someone innocently touches someone else.
就会有火花
There's electricity.
那感觉很新鲜  很刺激
It's new. It's exciting.
你敢说完全没有可能...
Are you telling me there isn't even the slightest possibility...
...出事
...of something happening?
或许有  天哪
Maybe. Oh, my God.
听你说我才真的有些信了
I didn't really believe it until you just said it.
别的小朋友都不信  但我发誓  那只鸭子真的推了我
None of the other kids believed me, I swear to God, that duck pushed me.
哇  这地方真豪华
Wow. This place is fabulous.
我带你参观  这是楼下的客厅
Yeah, let me show you around. This is the downstairs living room.
这有两个客厅
There's two living rooms?
天啊  你靠这里把到好多美眉吧
God, growing up here, this place must have been a real babe magnet.
啊  应该会  但我父母刚搬来
Yeah, well, it would have been, but, uh, my parents just moved here.
你一定靠这里把到了很多美眉
Well, you should know this place is a real babe magnet.
要亲热吗
Want to make out?
这样吧  我干吗不把东西先放进冰箱里
You know, here's an idea. Why don't I put the food in the fridge...
等我们待会儿再吃
...and we can eat it later?
听起来不错
That sounds like a plan. Heh.
哪里可以让我梳洗一下
Um, is there a place that I could go freshen up?
有   直走左边第二个门
Oh, yeah. Yeah. Um, just down the hall and, uh, second door to your left.
儿子  爸妈  你们怎么回来了
Oh, hi, darling. Mom, Dad, what are you guys doing here?
我们提前结束行程  法国烂透了
Oh, we cut the trip short. France sucks.
现在情况有点特殊   我带了人回来
Um, this may be a little weird, but I've got a date here.
了解
Say no more.
我们拿了吃的  就上楼不妨碍你
We'll just grab some food, take it with us upstairs and be out of your hair.
那就好  所以你们也不去意大利了
Oh, that'd be great. So you didn't even get to Italy?
没有  意大利也烂
Yep. Sucks.
你来了
Hi, you.
啊  天哪
Oh, my God.
我知道  我不只会做菜
I know. I can do more than cook.
我喜欢她  她似乎很聪明
I like her. She seems smart.
瑞秋  我爸妈
Rachel, my parents.
很高兴认识你们  哈罗  哈罗
So nice to meet you. Hello, hello.
约书亚  那5百元是给你买日用品的
Oh, Joshua, that $500 was for groceries.
什么  这不  你们误会了
What, this? Oh, no. That's not what it is.
我在时装界工作
Okay, I work in fashion.
实际上  这才是正式的时装
See, and this is a real dress, actually.
米兰正在流行
They're wearing it in Milan.
所以我也必须试穿衣服  观察一般人的反应
So part of my job is to wear the clothes and then I see how people respond.
然后汇报给布鲁明戴尔的上司
And then I report back to my superiors at Bloomingdale's, so...
不过这次
And obviously, in this case...
我显然得汇报说
...I am going to report back:
"美国  尚嫌大胆"
"U.S.A. Not ready."
洛杉矶或许可以
Maybe in L.A. Yes.
有道理  你们吃过饭了吗
There you go. So have you kids eaten yet?
我们想等事后  不是
Well, ahem, we were going to do that after. I mean, um...
接着  正好  我们也饿死了
Next. Well, we're starving.
不如大家一起出去吃吧
Why don't we just all go get something to eat?
也好  穿着它窝在家里太可惜了
Yeah, well, ha, ha, no use wasting this baby just lying around the house.
所以我们去吃饭  对啊
So we'll go eat. Yeah.
你就穿那样
You'll wear that.
我们去吃饭  你就穿那样吃饭
We'll be eating and, of course, you'll be wearing that.
我为我说的话道歉
Dude, I am sorry about what I said.
不  不  你说得对 这个名字太可笑了
Nope, nope, you're right. It is a ridiculous name.
也没那么糟   当然有了
It's not that bad. Yes, it is.
从现在开始  我只有姓没有名了
From now on, I have no first name.
你就叫宾
So you're just Bing?
我无名无姓
I have no name.
那我们要叫你什么
So, what are we supposed to call you?
好  你们就暂时叫我…
Okay, uh, for now, temporarily, you can call me...
克林顿
...Clint.
你才不够酷叫 "克林顿"
No way are you cool enough to pull off "Clint."
那我可以叫什么
Okay, so, what name am I cool enough to pull off?
嗯  金
Um, Gene.
克林顿  就是克林顿
It's Clint. It's Clint.
金  再见  金  再见
See you later, Gene. Bye, Gene.
是克林顿   克林顿
It's Clint. Clint!
金有什么不好
What's up with Gene?
你穿你的睡衣去吃饭   没错
You wore your nightie to dinner? Oh, yeah.
最精彩的是  我背后被服务生泼到水时
And the best part though, was when the waiter spilled water down my back.
我一跳  咪咪就弹了出来
I jumped up and my boob popped out.
哇  天啊  不
Oh, my God. Oh, no.
好惨  没关系  我的胸型很漂亮
Yeah, it's all right. I got nice boobs.
我刚收到艾蜜莉的留言
So I just picked up a message from Emily.
她要和苏珊要一起去读诗会
She and Susan are going to a poetry reading together.
所以呢  所以呢
So? So?
诗
Poetry?
苏珊是同志
Susan's gay.
她们志同道合
They're being gay together.
艾蜜莉是异性恋  你醒醒吧
Emily's straight. Oh, wake up.
哇
Wow.
卡萝真的把你害惨了
Carol really messed you up.
你说什么
Excuse me?
她害你变成不信任别人   疯疯癫癫爱吃醋
She turned you into this untrusting, crazy, jealous sycophant.
我不知道爱吃醋是什么  但其他都没说错
All right, so I don't know what "sycophant" means, but the rest is right.
我不知道你要说啥  我哪有疯疯癫癫爱吃醋
I don't know what you're talking about. I am not a crazy, jealous person.
什么   她说得没错
What? She's totally right.
我们以前  你老爱吃马克的醋
When we were together, you got all freaked out about Mark...
其实根本没事  有道理
...and there was nothing going on. This makes sense.
才怪
It does not.
当然有道理  高中时你每个女友都不忠
Sure it does. In high school, you weren't jealous at all...
你也没吃过醋
...even though all your girlfriends were cheating on you.
直到92  93年 他都很信任别人
All right, so up until '92, '93, he was very trusting.
然后94年  卡萝离开他  砰  纽约鬼影幢幢
Then '94 hit, Carol left him, and bam. Paranoid City.
是的
Yeah.
就是这样  就是这样
Absolutely, absolutely.
好好玩
This is so much fun.
一点也不好玩
This is not fun.
我们只想说
Look, all we're trying to say is...
别让你和卡萝的事  破坏你和艾蜜莉的感情
...don't let what happened with Carol ruin what you've got with Emily.
92年的罗斯就不会
The '92 Ross wouldn't.
我还是觉得马克定有问题
I still think I was right about that whole Mark thing, though.
什么  你知道吗   我希望艾蜜莉是同志
Wha...? Well, you know what? I hope Emily is a lesbian.
击鼓
Drum roll.
行了  行了
Okay. Okay.
这样
All right.
帮个忙  我是马克还是约翰
Help. Am I a Mark or a John?
你当马克不够高
Ehh, you're not tall enough to be a Mark.
你或许可以当个好巴尼
But you might make a good Barney.
拜托  我是认真的
All right, look, I am serious.
明天3点半我就要上法院
Tomorrow at 3:30, I'm going to the courthouse.
你真的要改名
You're actually going through with this?
这个名字拖累了我一辈子
Hey, look, this name has been holding me back my entire life.
害的我被其他小朋友找喳  女人运也很差
Okay, it's probably why kids picked on me in school, and why I never do well with women.
明天4点起  我不是马克约翰森  就是约翰马克森
So as of 4:00 tomorrow, I'm either gonna be Mark Johnson or John Markson.
你的问题在于你自己   与名字无关
You've got problems because of you, not your name.
别再闹了  钱德这个名字很棒
This has got to stop. Chandler is a great name.
事实上
In fact...
好
Yes.
对不起  我知道你希望宝宝叫乔伊
I'm sorry, I know you really wanted me to name the baby Joey.
但我要  我要让他叫钱德
But... So I'm gonna name the baby Chandler.
真的
Really?
对  但你也得保留这个名字
Yeah, but you have to keep the name too.
好  谢了
Okay, thanks. Okay.
要不要抱下  好
You want to hug it out? Yeah.
我现在就去告诉法兰克他们
Okay, I'm gonna go tell Frank and Alice right now.
好的
Okay.
菲比  再见  再见
Bye, Pheebs. Okay, bye.
004班机已到达17号门
Flight 004 is now arriving at Gate 17.
很棒的行李箱  我正要说
Nice luggage. I was going to say.
嗨  嘿
Hey. Hi.
我好想你  我也是
I missed you. Oh, I missed you too.
谢谢你  我玩得很开心
Thanks for everything, I had a great time.
我也是
Oh, so did I.
不是舌吻
No tongue.